<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>/competition-and-collaboration-cakes</loc>
    <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
    <priority>0.75</priority>
    <lastmod>2021-07-12</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/t/60ec7369f89f8e700bf5d369/1510176226111/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Tinker for The Magical Dragon Machine Display at Cake International Birmingham NEC 2017</image:title>
      <image:caption>Tinker - a 12" Victorian Child Figure, made with Modelling Paste, decorated with flower paste, cake lace and isomalt. The Magical Dragon Machine was created for a display at Cake International Birmingham NEC 2017, to support Coffee4Craig Charity. Photo taken by Roger Peaple Photography.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5a03412ce4966b1a48af1167/1510176226111/tinkerlogobyroger_Fotor.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Tinker for The Magical Dragon Machine Display at Cake International Birmingham NEC 2017</image:title>
      <image:caption>Tinker - a 12" Victorian Child Figure, made with Modelling Paste, decorated with flower paste, cake lace and isomalt. The Magical Dragon Machine was created for a display at Cake International Birmingham NEC 2017, to support Coffee4Craig Charity. Photo taken by Roger Peaple Photography.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5a037f3fe2c483e53caf3bae/1510178749404/Collage_Fotorfinaltinkerpiece_Fotor.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Tinker and her tools</image:title>
      <image:caption>12" Victorian Child carrying her steampunk style tools to build the Magical Dragon Machine.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5a0380238165f535a0984ce5/1510179148389/final.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Victorian Lady on a swing</image:title>
      <image:caption>12" Victorian lady on a swing, made with Saracino modelling paste, decorated with gumpaste and royal icing, and her hair was made with corn silk. Last minute piece created for Cake International Birmingham NEC 2017. Silver Award.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5877981fe6f2e1b3ddc66dc2/1484263573175/Marisa_Kemp_black_masquerade_wm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Black Masquerade</image:title>
      <image:caption>This collaboration piece was inspired by the Black Masquerade, one of the Divas illustrations created by the acclaimed and talented Fairy and Fantasy Artist: “Maxine Gadd”. This is a structured bust cover with homemade chocolate and sugar paste. For the decorations, I used gumpaste, sugarpaste, royal icing, isomalt and cake lace. Totally edible, with exception of the wired flowers. It was a real pleasure to take part in The Sugar Myths and Fantasies Global Edition collaboration alongside over 120 talented artists from all over the world!!</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587800bc59cc686e626704f6/1484263586802/Collage_Fotorcollabpieces3.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Black Masquerade</image:title>
      <image:caption>Some extra photos of the Black Masquerade piece.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5877d6b503596e6a0a292d2c/1484334966888/IMG_0391+%281%29.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Steampunk Lady</image:title>
      <image:caption>Decorative exhibit entered for Cake International Birmingham Competition 2016 - Awarded Gold. Steampunk lady structure bust, covered with homemade chocolate and sugar paste, decorated with modelling, sugar, and mexican paste, some royal icing, cake lace and isomalt.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5877fc13e6f2e1e0d8dd3de4/1484263609099/Collage_Fotorsteampunk.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Steampunk Lady</image:title>
      <image:caption>Some extra photos of the Steampunk Lady piece.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5877edcb2994ca68e906b72d/1484263619792/IMG_3415.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Engagement Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Celebration entry for Cake International Alexander Palace London, awarded Silver. 2 tier covered in sugarpaste, decorated with royal icing and some sugarpaste daises on a pastillage vase on top. The royal icing decorations include some lambeth technique, scrolls, and line and string work, with run-out designs.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587801203a0411969c704e1d/1484263626274/Collage_Fotorstainlesssteal.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>3 tier Wedding Cake entry for Squires Kitchen Competition 2016. This is covered in sugarpaste and decorated with royal icing details including some lambeth technique, scrolls, line and run-out work and some pastillage for the gazebo. For the steainless steal windows effect, I used some piping gel around royal icing, modelling paste for the bride and groom owl models and gumpaste for the flowers inside of the pastillage vase, inside the gazebo. I was awarded a 'Commended" certificate for this cake.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587809a2ff7c506c43a85e26/1484421262285/royalicingcelebration2015.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Celebration Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>A single tier celebration cake entry for Cake International Excel London 2015. Cake covered in sugarpaste, decorated with royal icing, bridge and line work, a sugarpaste designed panel underneith, some deises and butterflies made with gumpaste and an abstract semi circle royal icing work on top of cake. I was awarded a Bronze certificate.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587805ae6b8f5bb797889134/1484263637228/oldhollywoodglamourweddingcake2015a.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Old Hollywood Glamour Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my entry for Squires Kitchen Competition 2015. 2 tier cake covered in sugarpaste and decorated with royal icing and some pastillage for the stairs, covered with gumpaste and decorated with royal icing. The couple on top is hand modelled with modelling paste, dressed with gumpaste and royal icing string work for the brides hair ornament. I was awarded First Price on this class with this cake!</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5878086acd0f689b62666cd2/1484421202042/minicake2015a.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Miniature Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>My entry for Squires Kitchen Competition 2015. 2 tier miniature cake (to fit within 6" square), covered in sugarpaste and decorated with royal icing, with some lambeth technique, bridge, line and string work, with 3 piped red roses. I was awarded a "Commended" certificate with this cake.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587803c92994ca1c590d9b3b/1484439096966/Collage_Fotorgoldroyalicing3.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Celebration Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my entry for Cake International Excel in London 2014. It was a celebration cake covered and decorated with royal icing. I decorated with oriental string work and place a pastillage mat and vase on top for with a pastillage vase and gumpaste daisies inside. I was awarded Gold and placed 2nd place for this class.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/58780df16a4963fee2dab863/1484263659742/IMG_2995.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Wedding cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>3 tier Wedding Cake entry for Cake International Excel London 2014. Cake covered in sugarpaste, painted and airbrushed then decorated with some a huge gumpaste blue rose and petals falling from it. I was awarded a "Certificate of Merit".</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/58780adcf5e231c32fe82d75/1484263665744/IMG_2997.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Celebration Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Celebration Cake entry for NSA (National Sugar Association) Competition 2014. This cake was covered and decorated with royal icing, including some lambeth technique and string, line and lace work, andpiped roses on top. I was awarded 2 Prize on this class.  </image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd87b71c7c440001a00944/1560119948757/IMG_8480.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - The Queen's Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Here you can see the replica of The Queen’s Wedding cake on the left and on the right the newly restored version created by various members of The British Sugarcraft Guild (including myself).</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd8b2540541300018dc7e2/1626085742196/IMG_8479.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - The Queen's Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>This is the award-winning Queen’s Wedding Cake Project that I have proudly taken part on with members of The British Sugarcraft Guild across the UK, and is displayed at The Peek Freans Museum in Bermondsey.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd8cda2ad8ec0001e95996/1560120952837/IMG_9280.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Calebs Courage for "Amore - a heart for children collaboration"</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my piece inspired by Caleb MacArthur’s story @CalebsCourage, a 3 year old boy who knew the true meaning of being a superhero.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd9494687825000153294e/1560122598460/romeonjulietwm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Romeo and Juliet for Cake International Birmingham 2018</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my small decorative exhibit for the Cake International Birmingham 2018.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd8e929b08a0000184ade7/1560121545019/IMG_0967.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Bald Ballerina for "I Guerrieri Collaboration"</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my piece for “I Guerrieri” Collaboration, inspired by Maggie Kudirka, whom at the age of 23 and a dancer for the Joffrey Concert Group in NYC, in 2014, was diagnosed with metastatic (stage 4) breast cancer. After undergone chemotherapy and double mastectomy, she was back in the dance studio only 6 days after surgery. Maggie and her family set up a donation website to help with her mounting expenses, which she will need for the rest of her life or until a cure is found. She teaches Ballet master classes and shares her story to raise awareness and funds for breast cancer treatment and research.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd90ea5ce11200013a88a3/1560122046658/IMG_6591.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - World Water Day for "Amore - a future for our children" collaboration</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my piece created for the “Amore - a future for our children” collaboration, revealed on the World Water Day (22nd March ‘19).</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd92d668875a00015a922a/1560122342925/meditatingindiantablewm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Meditating Indian for "The Essense of India" Competition</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my piece for the Orpington branch table for the British Sugarcraft Guild Exhibition - Region 8 - in Brighton May’19.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd93f183556b0001a3768c/1560122476797/indianladywm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Indian lady for "The Essence of India" Competition</image:title>
      <image:caption>Another piece for the Essence of India Orpigton Branch Table, for the The British Sugarcraft Guild Region 8 Exhibition in Brighton May’19.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5d5888a4f708ac0001877d81/1566083611171/IMG_7795.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Brunette Burlesque Figure</image:title>
      <image:caption>This is a Sugarjunkies collaboration to celebrate Brulesque. This piece was created using Saracino Pasta Model, Squires Royal Icing Mix Powder, Cake Lace, Global Sugar Artists Network Brushes, Sugarflair Colours and The Sugar Paste sugarpaste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5d588a35fbeeb0000188d214/1566083729259/burlesquecollagecalogo.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Brunette Burlesque Figure</image:title>
      <image:caption>More photos of my Burlesque piece, created for The Burlesque Collaboration.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5dcde0faa2a8163035f95497/1573775220242/MarisaKemp1.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - "Ursula" - piece created for the Sugar Witches Display</image:title>
      <image:caption>“Ursula” was inspired on a post from the Dark Beauty magazine, from 12th October, 2015, photographer: Sandra Bluhm - Licht und Schattenspiel, model: Gatto Nero Katzenkunst. This piece was created using Saracino Pasta Model, Saracino Cioccolato Plastico Bianco, Saracino Colour Powder, Saracino Isomalt, Cake Lace, Global Sugar Artists Network brushes, Cerart and PME Tools. Hope you like her.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5dcde1d7f2def3754797d307/1573773997877/MarisaKemp3.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - "Ursula" - my piece for the Sugar Witches Collaboration</image:title>
      <image:caption>A better close up of "Ursula’s face”. She was on display at Cake International NEC Birmingham, 2019.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5dcde71df2def37547987941/1626108777908/ursula_collage2.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Ursula</image:title>
      <image:caption>Different angles of Ursula displayed at Cake International Birmingham, NEC, 2019.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec503cbc1dbf0eb2ec29a7/1626102460203/final%2B%25282%2529.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - La Plume Painting</image:title>
      <image:caption>This is one of my pieces for the Art Nouveau Meets Cake Artist Collaboration hosted by Sharon Siriwardena</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec5d308519c641af82f353/1626103297071/final.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - La Plume - Mucha</image:title>
      <image:caption>Another piece I created for the Art Nouveau Meets Cake Artist Collaboration hosted by Sharon Siriwardena</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec5e7f01b7823f78d4afef/1626103744557/final+%2814%29.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Jen's shoe</image:title>
      <image:caption>My piece for A Mother’s Day Collaboration - in memory of Jennifer Lofthouse organised by The Sugar Junkies.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec6019f499ab3cd9d6578d/1626106460191/IMG_4427.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Lavradeira do Minho</image:title>
      <image:caption>Portuguese girl of Viana do Castelo, Minho, 9” figure created for the Portugal Wonders in Sugar Collaboration hosted by Elisabete Caseiro.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec68d61461bf1e5dc7f090/1626108402544/final+%2812%29.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Ben De La Creme</image:title>
      <image:caption>This is my Ben De La Creme piece created for the Sugar Drag Collaboration hosted by Vicky Teather.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec695af4a9bc72a9c67de0/1626108508041/IMG_5016.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competition and Collaboration Cakes - Ben De La Creme</image:title>
      <image:caption>Different angles of my Ben De La Creme sugar piece.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>/toppers</loc>
    <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
    <priority>0.75</priority>
    <lastmod>2019-08-17</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/t/5d5887e9bb302e00015578b3/1484411346916/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Chanel inspired sugar shoe topper</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b740ee4b03548fe32c665/1484411346916/IMG_9652.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Chanel inspired sugar shoe topper</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b73e9e4b079203edc8470/1484439820782/IMG_9723.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Bride and Groom Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/58794518cd0f6821ffd25b1a/1484342552432/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/59652525e6f2e1757d50c48a/1499801097929/Collage_Fotorsteampunklady_Fotor.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - 12" Lady topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>12" topper figure made with Saracino modelling paste, Satin Ice gum paste, Cake Lace, Rainbow Dust Colours, Innovative Sugarworks and PME tools.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b7441e4b03548fe32c783/1484439820797/IMG_3098.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Little Snoopy topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Snoopy sleeping on top of his dog house</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b744be4b0ada2351a5b76/1484439820808/IMG_1990.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Super Mario and Princess Peach Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Wedding Couple topper.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b7444e4b079203edc868b/1484439821012/IMG_2438.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - 2d Aquarius Zodiac Sign Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Topper created for the West Wickham Sugarcraft Club, table display for the National SugarArt Association, which with many other members club team pieces, got us 1st prize in 2014.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5550abc6e4b09c3867896f76/1484439820784/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Wedding Cats Couple Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Wedding cake topper resembling the Aristocats.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/556e22a9e4b00d4b300e1039/1484439820842/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Art Nouveau Painting</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c500e4b001b264ef1813/1484439820763/IMG_0063.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Christian Louboutin Pastillage Shoe Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Pastillage shoe with gumpaste cloth on a sugar board, size 5, made without a shoe mould.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c50fe4b0e9f25c89a49a/1484439820976/IMG_0083.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Victorian Style Toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>Fountain, chair and vase with flowers made with pastillage and little peasant and butterflies made with modelling paste</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c51ae4b053bc20ccf3bc/1484439821208/IMG_0097.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Baby Jake topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Topper made with modelling paste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c514e4b001b264ef1856/1484440087884/IMG_0089.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Baby in a basket</image:title>
      <image:caption>Tiny baby in a Moses basket made with modelling paste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c526e4b035612aa5fcdf/1484439821208/IMG_0107.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Grandpa's topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Mini figure of a grandpa, based on his photo and his surroundings. I used some RKT (Rice Krispies Treats) for his armchair and modelled his figure and little dog with modelling paste and printed his newspaper and rug on icing sugar sheets.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c52ce4b0e9f25c89a504/1484439821210/IMG_0113.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Bride and Groom Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c52ce4b001b264ef18bc/1484439821225/IMG_0114.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Royal icing terrier topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Dog made with modelling paste and covered with piped royal icing.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c533e4b0d194ae3d86c3/1484439821641/IMG_0120.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - 70's style toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>Toppers made with modelling paste,  RKT (rice krispies treats) for the phone, rubics cube, Pacmanand Snoopy's house.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5579d322e4b0c48a5c322200/1484439821295/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Mafia Hippos Toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>Toppers made with modelling paste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5579d989e4b0b2fbee79b301/1484439821305/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Owls couple toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>Bride and Groom owls made with sugarpaste</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5579d9a8e4b01eeef8e24d34/1484439821423/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Cute Clown topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Topper made with modelling paste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b7411e4b02fb38e08026e/1484439821427/IMG_9579.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Large white rose topper</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b742ce4b0ada2351a5acd/1484439821431/IMG_7078.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Cake Angel Christmas toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>I have modelled my logo for Christmas and added a little Christmas tree to place on top of our family Christmas cake.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c50ce4b0e9f25c89a48f/1484439821433/IMG_0079.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Airbrushed cupcakes</image:title>
      <image:caption>20 different stencil designs for cupcakes. All covered with sugarpaste and airbrushed.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5cfd96335d605c0001df5a98/1560123038839/DSC_0587.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Santa Claus Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Small Santa Claus topper created for family Christmas Cake.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5cfd96c32b75660001302d99/1560123206978/IMG_1712.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - 7" Blossom Girl figure</image:title>
      <image:caption>Small Figure created for a workshop.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5cfd97859b08a0000184dc8e/1560123540323/indianladieswm+copy.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Meditating Ladies</image:title>
      <image:caption>6” Indian figures wearing a sari, created for demonstrations and workshops.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5cfd98b00c4dee00016cfd2f/1560123673320/demostainedglasswm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Stained Glass Effect using Piping Gel</image:title>
      <image:caption>Topper created for demonstrations.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5d588715750ae8000172132d/1566083049616/flowersbouquetwm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Toppers - Tropical Flowers Bouquet</image:title>
      <image:caption>Cake topper created for a Jamaican designed cake. Used Squires Flower Paste, PME cutters and Sugarflair Dust Colours.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>/maingallery</loc>
    <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
    <priority>0.75</priority>
    <lastmod>2017-01-15</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec695af4a9bc72a9c67de0/1626108508041/IMG_5016.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Ben De La Creme</image:title>
      <image:caption>Different angles of my Ben De La Creme sugar piece.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec68d61461bf1e5dc7f090/1626108402544/final+%2812%29.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Ben De La Creme</image:title>
      <image:caption>This is my Ben De La Creme piece created for the Sugar Drag Collaboration hosted by Vicky Teather.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec6019f499ab3cd9d6578d/1626106460191/IMG_4427.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Lavradeira do Minho</image:title>
      <image:caption>Portuguese girl of Viana do Castelo, Minho, 9” figure created for the Portugal Wonders in Sugar Collaboration hosted by Elisabete Caseiro.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec5e7f01b7823f78d4afef/1626103744557/final+%2814%29.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Jen's shoe</image:title>
      <image:caption>My piece for A Mother’s Day Collaboration - in memory of Jennifer Lofthouse organised by The Sugar Junkies.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec5d308519c641af82f353/1626103297071/final.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - La Plume - Mucha</image:title>
      <image:caption>Another piece I created for the Art Nouveau Meets Cake Artist Collaboration hosted by Sharon Siriwardena</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/60ec503cbc1dbf0eb2ec29a7/1626102460203/final%2B%25282%2529.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - La Plume Painting</image:title>
      <image:caption>This is one of my pieces for the Art Nouveau Meets Cake Artist Collaboration hosted by Sharon Siriwardena</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5dcde71df2def37547987941/1626108777908/ursula_collage2.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Ursula</image:title>
      <image:caption>Different angles of Ursula displayed at Cake International Birmingham, NEC, 2019.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5dcde1d7f2def3754797d307/1573773997877/MarisaKemp3.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - "Ursula" - my piece for the Sugar Witches Collaboration</image:title>
      <image:caption>A better close up of "Ursula’s face”. She was on display at Cake International NEC Birmingham, 2019.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5dcde0faa2a8163035f95497/1573775220242/MarisaKemp1.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - "Ursula" - piece created for the Sugar Witches Display</image:title>
      <image:caption>“Ursula” was inspired on a post from the Dark Beauty magazine, from 12th October, 2015, photographer: Sandra Bluhm - Licht und Schattenspiel, model: Gatto Nero Katzenkunst. This piece was created using Saracino Pasta Model, Saracino Cioccolato Plastico Bianco, Saracino Colour Powder, Saracino Isomalt, Cake Lace, Global Sugar Artists Network brushes, Cerart and PME Tools. Hope you like her.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5d588a35fbeeb0000188d214/1566083729259/burlesquecollagecalogo.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Brunette Burlesque Figure</image:title>
      <image:caption>More photos of my Burlesque piece, created for The Burlesque Collaboration.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5d5888a4f708ac0001877d81/1566083611171/IMG_7795.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Brunette Burlesque Figure</image:title>
      <image:caption>This is a Sugarjunkies collaboration to celebrate Brulesque. This piece was created using Saracino Pasta Model, Squires Royal Icing Mix Powder, Cake Lace, Global Sugar Artists Network Brushes, Sugarflair Colours and The Sugar Paste sugarpaste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd9494687825000153294e/1560122598460/romeonjulietwm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Romeo and Juliet for Cake International Birmingham 2018</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my small decorative exhibit for the Cake International Birmingham 2018.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd93f183556b0001a3768c/1560122476797/indianladywm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Indian lady for "The Essence of India" Competition</image:title>
      <image:caption>Another piece for the Essence of India Orpigton Branch Table, for the The British Sugarcraft Guild Region 8 Exhibition in Brighton May’19.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd92d668875a00015a922a/1560122342925/meditatingindiantablewm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Meditating Indian for "The Essense of India" Competition</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my piece for the Orpington branch table for the British Sugarcraft Guild Exhibition - Region 8 - in Brighton May’19.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd90ea5ce11200013a88a3/1560122046658/IMG_6591.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - World Water Day for "Amore - a future for our children" collaboration</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my piece created for the “Amore - a future for our children” collaboration, revealed on the World Water Day (22nd March ‘19).</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd8e929b08a0000184ade7/1560121545019/IMG_0967.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Bald Ballerina for "I Guerrieri Collaboration"</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my piece for “I Guerrieri” Collaboration, inspired by Maggie Kudirka, whom at the age of 23 and a dancer for the Joffrey Concert Group in NYC, in 2014, was diagnosed with metastatic (stage 4) breast cancer. After undergone chemotherapy and double mastectomy, she was back in the dance studio only 6 days after surgery. Maggie and her family set up a donation website to help with her mounting expenses, which she will need for the rest of her life or until a cure is found. She teaches Ballet master classes and shares her story to raise awareness and funds for breast cancer treatment and research.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd8cda2ad8ec0001e95996/1560120952837/IMG_9280.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Calebs Courage for "Amore - a heart for children collaboration"</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my piece inspired by Caleb MacArthur’s story @CalebsCourage, a 3 year old boy who knew the true meaning of being a superhero.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd8b2540541300018dc7e2/1626085742196/IMG_8479.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - The Queen's Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>This is the award-winning Queen’s Wedding Cake Project that I have proudly taken part on with members of The British Sugarcraft Guild across the UK, and is displayed at The Peek Freans Museum in Bermondsey.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5cfd87b71c7c440001a00944/1560119948757/IMG_8480.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - The Queen's Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Here you can see the replica of The Queen’s Wedding cake on the left and on the right the newly restored version created by various members of The British Sugarcraft Guild (including myself).</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5a0380238165f535a0984ce5/1510179148389/final.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Victorian Lady on a swing</image:title>
      <image:caption>12" Victorian lady on a swing, made with Saracino modelling paste, decorated with gumpaste and royal icing, and her hair was made with corn silk. Last minute piece created for Cake International Birmingham NEC 2017. Silver Award.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5a037f3fe2c483e53caf3bae/1510178749404/Collage_Fotorfinaltinkerpiece_Fotor.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Tinker and her tools</image:title>
      <image:caption>12" Victorian Child carrying her steampunk style tools to build the Magical Dragon Machine.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5a03412ce4966b1a48af1167/1510176226111/tinkerlogobyroger_Fotor.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Tinker for The Magical Dragon Machine Display at Cake International Birmingham NEC 2017</image:title>
      <image:caption>Tinker - a 12" Victorian Child Figure, made with Modelling Paste, decorated with flower paste, cake lace and isomalt. The Magical Dragon Machine was created for a display at Cake International Birmingham NEC 2017, to support Coffee4Craig Charity. Photo taken by Roger Peaple Photography.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/58780adcf5e231c32fe82d75/1484263665744/IMG_2997.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Celebration Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Celebration Cake entry for NSA (National Sugar Association) Competition 2014. This cake was covered and decorated with royal icing, including some lambeth technique and string, line and lace work, andpiped roses on top. I was awarded 2 Prize on this class.  </image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/58780df16a4963fee2dab863/1484263659742/IMG_2995.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Wedding cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>3 tier Wedding Cake entry for Cake International Excel London 2014. Cake covered in sugarpaste, painted and airbrushed then decorated with some a huge gumpaste blue rose and petals falling from it. I was awarded a "Certificate of Merit".</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587803c92994ca1c590d9b3b/1484439096966/Collage_Fotorgoldroyalicing3.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Celebration Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my entry for Cake International Excel in London 2014. It was a celebration cake covered and decorated with royal icing. I decorated with oriental string work and place a pastillage mat and vase on top for with a pastillage vase and gumpaste daisies inside. I was awarded Gold and placed 2nd place for this class.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5878086acd0f689b62666cd2/1484421202042/minicake2015a.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Miniature Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>My entry for Squires Kitchen Competition 2015. 2 tier miniature cake (to fit within 6" square), covered in sugarpaste and decorated with royal icing, with some lambeth technique, bridge, line and string work, with 3 piped red roses. I was awarded a "Commended" certificate with this cake.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587805ae6b8f5bb797889134/1484263637228/oldhollywoodglamourweddingcake2015a.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Old Hollywood Glamour Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>This was my entry for Squires Kitchen Competition 2015. 2 tier cake covered in sugarpaste and decorated with royal icing and some pastillage for the stairs, covered with gumpaste and decorated with royal icing. The couple on top is hand modelled with modelling paste, dressed with gumpaste and royal icing string work for the brides hair ornament. I was awarded First Price on this class with this cake!</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587809a2ff7c506c43a85e26/1484421262285/royalicingcelebration2015.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Celebration Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>A single tier celebration cake entry for Cake International Excel London 2015. Cake covered in sugarpaste, decorated with royal icing, bridge and line work, a sugarpaste designed panel underneith, some deises and butterflies made with gumpaste and an abstract semi circle royal icing work on top of cake. I was awarded a Bronze certificate.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587801203a0411969c704e1d/1484263626274/Collage_Fotorstainlesssteal.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>3 tier Wedding Cake entry for Squires Kitchen Competition 2016. This is covered in sugarpaste and decorated with royal icing details including some lambeth technique, scrolls, line and run-out work and some pastillage for the gazebo. For the steainless steal windows effect, I used some piping gel around royal icing, modelling paste for the bride and groom owl models and gumpaste for the flowers inside of the pastillage vase, inside the gazebo. I was awarded a 'Commended" certificate for this cake.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5877edcb2994ca68e906b72d/1484263619792/IMG_3415.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Engagement Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Celebration entry for Cake International Alexander Palace London, awarded Silver. 2 tier covered in sugarpaste, decorated with royal icing and some sugarpaste daises on a pastillage vase on top. The royal icing decorations include some lambeth technique, scrolls, and line and string work, with run-out designs.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5877fc13e6f2e1e0d8dd3de4/1484263609099/Collage_Fotorsteampunk.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Steampunk Lady</image:title>
      <image:caption>Some extra photos of the Steampunk Lady piece.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5877d6b503596e6a0a292d2c/1484334966888/IMG_0391+%281%29.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Steampunk Lady</image:title>
      <image:caption>Decorative exhibit entered for Cake International Birmingham Competition 2016 - Awarded Gold. Steampunk lady structure bust, covered with homemade chocolate and sugar paste, decorated with modelling, sugar, and mexican paste, some royal icing, cake lace and isomalt.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/587800bc59cc686e626704f6/1484263586802/Collage_Fotorcollabpieces3.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Black Masquerade</image:title>
      <image:caption>Some extra photos of the Black Masquerade piece.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587797def5e231f7a6d21d02/5877981fe6f2e1b3ddc66dc2/1484263573175/Marisa_Kemp_black_masquerade_wm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces - Black Masquerade</image:title>
      <image:caption>This collaboration piece was inspired by the Black Masquerade, one of the Divas illustrations created by the acclaimed and talented Fairy and Fantasy Artist: “Maxine Gadd”. This is a structured bust cover with homemade chocolate and sugar paste. For the decorations, I used gumpaste, sugarpaste, royal icing, isomalt and cake lace. Totally edible, with exception of the wired flowers. It was a real pleasure to take part in The Sugar Myths and Fantasies Global Edition collaboration alongside over 120 talented artists from all over the world!!</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/t/58711c6637c5811e54c45380/1483808256662/Black+Masquerade+inspired+by+Maxine+Gadd%2C+created+for+Sugar+Myths+and+Fantasies+Global+Edition+Collaboration</image:loc>
      <image:title>Competitions and Collaboration Pieces</image:title>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>/home</loc>
    <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
    <priority>1.0</priority>
    <lastmod>2017-01-14</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/t/545d2e03e4b07fd6dcfe5ebb/1418226716029/marisa+stringwork+cake+cake+international++Screenshot+2014-11-05+13.01.14.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Creative Cake decoration.</image:title>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>/contact</loc>
    <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
    <priority>0.75</priority>
    <lastmod>2015-10-22</lastmod>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>/celebration-and-wedding-cakes</loc>
    <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
    <priority>0.75</priority>
    <lastmod>2017-09-10</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5cfd99da98f3530001a86512/1560124010379/stainedglasswm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Stained Glass Effect Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>2 tier cake decorated with stained glass effect technique, using piping gel.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/59b5697d49fc2b50d091efac/1505061315814/DSC_0531_Fotor.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - 3 Tiered Wedding Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Vanilla and Red Velvet Cake covered with sugarpaste and decorated with Royal Icing</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b7437e4b022bdc70eba4b/1484328253823/IMG_7464.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Steampunk hat cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Sculpted hat cake covered with sugarpaste, decorated with cake lace and a red rose.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b742ee4b03548fe32c70c/1484328042728/IMG_6606.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Chocolate ganache sponge with gold decoration</image:title>
      <image:caption>Chocolate ganache sponge, covered with ganache and decorated with gold cake lace, and a red rose on top.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b742be4b02fb38e0802f0/1484327661161/IMG_7075.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Royal iced white and gold cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Celebration cake covered and decorated with royal icing, with some lambeth technique, painted in gold.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b741ce4b0ada2351a5a6a/1484594062601/IMG_9465.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Silhouette celebration cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>3 tier cake covered with sugarpaste and decorated with some black leaves cuttings.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b741be4b0253bf445ea54/1484327268525/IMG_9466.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - 2 tier celebration cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Celebration cake decorated with cake lace and a large rose on top, and billows on bottom tier.  </image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b7419e4b0ada2351a5a66/1484327469494/IMG_9500.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Cherry tree wedding cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>3 tier cake covered with sugarpaste, decorated with 2 chocolate sculpted trees, with some cherry blossoms all around it.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b7417e4b0253bf445ea46/1484327372339/IMG_9501.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Black and white wedding cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>3 tier cake covered with sugarpaste and decorated with cake lace.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b7409e4b03548fe32c638/1484326962410/IMG_9702.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Madeira cake with vanilla butter frosting</image:title>
      <image:caption>Madeira cake with vanilla butter frosting and raspberry jam.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b7400e4b03548fe32c5f3/1484327029309/IMG_9704.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Chocolate Genoese Sponge</image:title>
      <image:caption>Chocolate genoese sponge with chocolate ganache filling.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b7404e4b079203edc8544/1484326592968/IMG_9705.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Black Forest Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b73f3e4b03548fe32c5ac/1484326562656/IMG_9709.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Sculpted sofa cake</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/555fc008e4b0c424d1632b54/1484326350097/IMG_9946.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Dolly, sculpted cake inspired by Carlos Lischetti's</image:title>
      <image:caption>Carlos Lischetti created Monty, the sheepdog, and he inspired me on creating Dolly.  </image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/554b73e4e4b022bdc70eb871/1484325012108/IMG_9732.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Royal iced inspired by porcelain design</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c522e4b035612aa5fcd4/1484387639697/IMG_0103.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Pegasus sculpture</image:title>
      <image:caption>Structure sculpture of a Pegasus made with RKT (Rice Krispies Treats) covered with sugarpaste and some gumpaste for the details.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c519e4b09a87487a2ed7/1484387143087/IMG_0094.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Art Nouveau (Mucha) painting</image:title>
      <image:caption>An 11" x 11" sugarpasted board painted with edible colour paste and colour dust mixed with a little of lemon extract for special effects, inspired on Feder artwork by Alphonse Mucha.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c517e4b0e9f25c89a4b1/1484347806971/IMG_0093.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Christmas cake with poinsettia Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Fruit cake covered with Marzipan and sugarpaste decorated with a gumpaste poinsettia.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c516e4b09a87487a2ed4/1484348502465/IMG_0091.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Present Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Chocolate sponge with chocolate buttercream, covered with sugarpaste, decorated with sugarpaste and gumpaste for the bow.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c514e4b09a87487a2ec9/1484348142241/IMG_0090.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Castle Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Chocolate sponge with white chocolate buttercream, covered with sugarpaste decorated with sugarpaste, royal icing(vine trees, details at doors and grass), pastillage (for the towers) and rice paper for the flags.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c50de4b0e9f25c89a491/1484346456707/IMG_0082.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Sculpted Pony</image:title>
      <image:caption>Fruit cake covered with sugarpaste with a sculpted pony made with RKT (Rice Krispies Treats) covered and modelled with sugarpaste.  </image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c50ae4b0e9f25c89a48d/1484346277976/IMG_0078.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Under the sea cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Gluten free cake covered with sugarpaste and decorated with some under the sea creatures, all created with my own templates and a 2d dolphin on top, made with modelling paste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c507e4b035612aa5fc67/1484387970959/IMG_0073.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Royal Icing cake e pastillage and isomalt</image:title>
      <image:caption>2 tier fruit cake covered with royal icing, decorated wiht oriental string work, some blossoms made of gumpaste, and a pastillage decoration with some isomalt on top.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c505e4b035612aa5fc65/1484346104144/IMG_0072.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Gardener boots Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Lemon Sponge Cake with lemon curd filling, covered with sugarpaste, decorated with 2 boots made with modelling paste and some mud impressions of dirty boots painted around the cake.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c506e4b0e9f25c89a483/1484345355983/IMG_0071.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Guinea Pig and Nurse's Hat Cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Lemon sponge cake with lemon curd filling, covered with sugarpaste and decorated with hand modelled hat and guinea pig made with modelling paste and some RKT(Rice Krispies Treats) for the hat.  </image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/5481c500e4b0e9f25c89a46e/1484344602193/IMG_0064.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Mockingjay Badge from the Hunger Games Film</image:title>
      <image:caption>Chocolate cake covered with sugarpaste, decorated with a sculpted 2d Mockingjay Badge from the Hunger Games Film, made with gumpaste and pastillage and painted in gold.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/55510f10e4b0c072ca67dcde/1484343803395/IMG_3056.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Royal Iced Cake with strings work</image:title>
      <image:caption>Sponge cake covered and decorated with royal icing.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/55510f06e4b0c072ca67dc9c/1484387927782/IMG_3055.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Homemade Chocolate Easter Eggs</image:title>
      <image:caption>I made 2 big Chocolate Easter Eggs and filled them in with small also homemade Easter Eggs and modelled a little Easter bunny with carrots and mini Easter eggs for Easter decorations.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/554b623be4b02fb38e07a9dc/55510f04e4b0c072ca67dc97/1484349476167/IMG_3054.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Celebration and Wedding Cakes - Rugby player birthday cake</image:title>
      <image:caption>Chocolate sponge cake with chocolate buttercream and raspberry jam covered with sugarpaste and chocolate gateau around it and a modelled rugby player on top, and rice paper flag.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>/cake-toppers</loc>
    <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
    <priority>0.75</priority>
    <lastmod>2017-01-14</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5d588715750ae8000172132d/1566083049616/flowersbouquetwm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Tropical Flowers Bouquet</image:title>
      <image:caption>Cake topper created for a Jamaican designed cake. Used Squires Flower Paste, PME cutters and Sugarflair Dust Colours.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5cfd98b00c4dee00016cfd2f/1560123673320/demostainedglasswm.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Stained Glass Effect using Piping Gel</image:title>
      <image:caption>Topper created for demonstrations.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5cfd97859b08a0000184dc8e/1560123540323/indianladieswm+copy.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Meditating Ladies</image:title>
      <image:caption>6” Indian figures wearing a sari, created for demonstrations and workshops.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5cfd96c32b75660001302d99/1560123206978/IMG_1712.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - 7" Blossom Girl figure</image:title>
      <image:caption>Small Figure created for a workshop.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5cfd96335d605c0001df5a98/1560123038839/DSC_0587.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Santa Claus Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Small Santa Claus topper created for family Christmas Cake.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/59652525e6f2e1757d50c48a/1499801097929/Collage_Fotorsteampunklady_Fotor.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - 12" Lady topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>12" topper figure made with Saracino modelling paste, Satin Ice gum paste, Cake Lace, Rainbow Dust Colours, Innovative Sugarworks and PME tools.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b744be4b0ada2351a5b76/1484439820808/IMG_1990.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Super Mario and Princess Peach Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Wedding Couple topper.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b7444e4b079203edc868b/1484439821012/IMG_2438.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - 2d Aquarius Zodiac Sign Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Topper created for the West Wickham Sugarcraft Club, table display for the National SugarArt Association, which with many other members club team pieces, got us 1st prize in 2014.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b7441e4b03548fe32c783/1484439820797/IMG_3098.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Little Snoopy topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Snoopy sleeping on top of his dog house</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b742ce4b0ada2351a5acd/1484439821431/IMG_7078.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Cake Angel Christmas toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>I have modelled my logo for Christmas and added a little Christmas tree to place on top of our family Christmas cake.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b7411e4b02fb38e08026e/1484439821427/IMG_9579.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Large white rose topper</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b73e9e4b079203edc8470/1484439820782/IMG_9723.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Bride and Groom Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/554b740ee4b03548fe32c665/1484411346916/IMG_9652.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Chanel inspired sugar shoe topper</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c533e4b0d194ae3d86c3/1484439821641/IMG_0120.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - 70's style toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>Toppers made with modelling paste,  RKT (rice krispies treats) for the phone, rubics cube, Pacmanand Snoopy's house.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c52ce4b001b264ef18bc/1484439821225/IMG_0114.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Royal icing terrier topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Dog made with modelling paste and covered with piped royal icing.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c52ce4b0e9f25c89a504/1484439821210/IMG_0113.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Bride and Groom Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c526e4b035612aa5fcdf/1484439821208/IMG_0107.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Grandpa's topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Mini figure of a grandpa, based on his photo and his surroundings. I used some RKT (Rice Krispies Treats) for his armchair and modelled his figure and little dog with modelling paste and printed his newspaper and rug on icing sugar sheets.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c514e4b001b264ef1856/1484440087884/IMG_0089.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Baby in a basket</image:title>
      <image:caption>Tiny baby in a Moses basket made with modelling paste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c51ae4b053bc20ccf3bc/1484439821208/IMG_0097.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Baby Jake topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Topper made with modelling paste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c50fe4b0e9f25c89a49a/1484439820976/IMG_0083.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Victorian Style Toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>Fountain, chair and vase with flowers made with pastillage and little peasant and butterflies made with modelling paste</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c50ce4b0e9f25c89a48f/1484439821433/IMG_0079.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Airbrushed cupcakes</image:title>
      <image:caption>20 different stencil designs for cupcakes. All covered with sugarpaste and airbrushed.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5481c500e4b001b264ef1813/1484439820763/IMG_0063.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Christian Louboutin Pastillage Shoe Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Pastillage shoe with gumpaste cloth on a sugar board, size 5, made without a shoe mould.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5579d9a8e4b01eeef8e24d34/1484439821423/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Cute Clown topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Topper made with modelling paste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5579d989e4b0b2fbee79b301/1484439821305/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Owls couple toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>Bride and Groom owls made with sugarpaste</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5579d322e4b0c48a5c322200/1484439821295/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Mafia Hippos Toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption>Toppers made with modelling paste.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/556e22a9e4b00d4b300e1039/1484439820842/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Art Nouveau Painting</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/5550abc6e4b09c3867896f76/1484439820784/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers - Wedding Cats Couple Topper</image:title>
      <image:caption>Wedding cake topper resembling the Aristocats.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>/static/545d2a91e4b043f3abfd2c21/587944562994ca9f4817cfb0/58794518cd0f6821ffd25b1a/1484342552432/</image:loc>
      <image:title>Cake Toppers</image:title>
      <image:caption />
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>/purchase-confirmation</loc>
    <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
    <priority>0.75</priority>
    <lastmod>2017-12-05</lastmod>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>/tutorials</loc>
    <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
    <priority>0.75</priority>
    <lastmod>2017-12-05</lastmod>
  </url>
</urlset>

